A Finding Aid to the Tibor de Nagy Gallery Records, 1941-2016, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, 1956-1993; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 18.6 Linear feet Boxes 13-31, 46
  - Pereire, Emmanuel, 1972-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Purcell, Ann, 1973-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 1-5)
  - Pollock, Jackson, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Porter, Fairfield, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Oversized material housed in OV 46
  - Poulos, Basilios, 1977-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 8-11)
  - Rand, Archie, 1969-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 12-21)
  - Regimento, Peter, 1970-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 1-12)
  - Richenburg, Robert, 1959-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Rivers, Larry - Information, Invoices, Billing, Business Correspondence, 1956-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Rivers, Larry - Business Correspondence and Larry Rivers Correspondence, 1958-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Rivers, Larry - Legal Proceedings, Marlborough, De Nagy, and Rivers, Correspondence, 1961-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Rivers, Larry - Photocopied Correspondence with Larry Rivers, 1959-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Rivers, Larry - Clippings and Publicity, 1956-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Rivers, Larry - Announcements, Catalogs, and Photographic Material, 1971-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Robbin, Tony, 1979-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 2-10)
  - Romberg, Osvaldo, 1982-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 11-13)
  - Rose, Leatrice, 1973-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 14-21)
  - Rosenblatt, Adolph, 1976-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 1-4)
    Contains 1 videocassette (VHS) Original label reads "Adolph Rosenblatt interview on exhibit 1981" [for Gallery Group Show (1982)]
  - Ross, Clifford, 1976-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 5-7)
  - Saito, Kikuo, 1966-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Scanga, Italo, 1982-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Schwedler, William, 1966-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 10-18)
  - Scott, Sam, 1977-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Scott, Tim, 1973-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 20-21)
  - Seidel, Jochen, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Shannon, Joe, 1967-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 23-24)
  - Shannon, Joe, 1967-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
  - Shaw, Kendall, 1965-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Stein, Ronald, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Stephen, Gary, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Stoltz, David Mark, 1971-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Stone, Sylvia, 1966-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 7-10)
  - Terry, Robert, 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 11-12)
  - Thomson, William, 1977-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Tillim, Sidney, 1977-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 14-15)
  - Torres, Horacio, 1973-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 16-20)
  - Tum Suden, Richard, 1962-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 21-24)
  - Tworkov, Jack, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Von Ringelheim, Paul, 1969-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Welliver, Neil, 1967-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - West, Pennerton, 1951-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Wilson, Jane, 1959-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 29-31)
  - Wisseman-Widrig, Nancy, 1972-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 1-7)
  - Woodman, Betty, circa 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Wurmfeld, Sanford, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Youlikis, Edward, 1976-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Oversized poster from Carriocchi, Ray - General and Transparancies; Box 15, Folder 12, Archival Resource Key (Box 46)
  - Oversized Poster from Goodnough, Robert - Bio, General; Box 16, Folder 36, Archival Resource Key (Box 46)
  - Oversize posters from Grooms, Red - Advertising and Publicity; Box 19, Folder 1, Archival Resource Key (Box 46)
  - Oversize poster from Lorentzen, Ida - Announcements, Catalogs, Poster; Box 23, Folder 12, Archival Resource Key (Box 46)
  - Oversize Poster from Porter, Fairfield - Poster; Box 26, Folder 7, Archival Resource Key (Box 46)
- Financial and Legal Records, 1951-1984; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 3.5 Linear feet Boxes 31-34
  Materials include mostly incomplete runs of billing procedures and statements, expenses and cash disbursements, paid and unpaid invoices, and sales and shipping receipts. There are also files on accountants used by the gallery, as well as legal actions including a lawsuit involving its landlord and other tenants, as well as a discrepancy of the gallery's name similar to another gallery.
  - Accounting, Jack Lichtenstein, 1969-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Accounting, Joseph Blau and Co., 1960-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Accounting, Joseph Blau and Co., Income Tax Returns, 1961-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Accounting, Joseph Gottfried, 1966-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Accounting, Scott, Mickelson Co., 1969-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Accounting, Taxes, 1958-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Billing, 1953-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 17-23)
  - Billing, 1964-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 1-11)
  - Billing, Invoices, 1961-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 12-13)
  - Billing, Paid Invoices, 1967-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 14-17)
  - Billing, Unpaid Invoices, 1967-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 18-19)
  - Expenses, Bills to Pay, 1968-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Expenses, Cash Disbursements, 1951-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 21-23)
  - Expenses, Cash Disbursements, 1960-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 1-5)
  - Expenses, Paid Bills, 1962-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 6-14)
  - Lawsuit, Parapsychology Foundation, Inc., 1971-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 15-16)
  - Legal Action, Eva de Nagy Gallery, 1960-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Legal Action, Suter, Roderic, 1967-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Receipts, Artworks Received, 1970-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 19-20)
  - Receipts, Artworks Shipped, 1971-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 21-28)
  - Sales Receipt Tags, 1963-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Carton 1)
- Inventory Records, 1952-1989; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 9 Linear feet Boxes 34-43
  Inventory records consist primarily of index cards and/or sheets that document stock, consignments, loans, sales, and shipping. Information on the inventory cards often includes artwork titles and description; inventory numbers; dates received, loaned, returned to artist, and sold; purchaser's names; some exhibition dates; prices; and notes of expressions of interest by clients. The most heavily represented artists include Rosemarie Castoro, Ray Ciarrocchi, Jane Freilicher, Robert Goodnough, Grace Hartigan, Joyce Kozloff, Rafael Mahdavi, Ann Purcell, Archie Rand, Peter Reginato, Larry Rivers, Richard Tum Suden, and Jane Wilson. Additionally, there is some material on the Houston branch gallery; additional Houston branch records are arranged in series 6.
  Arranged into 4 subseries based on subject groupings:
  5.1: Artist Cards, 1952-1989
  5.2: Works Returned to Artist, 1964-1989
  5.3: Sales, 1963-1989
  5.4: General Inventory, 1962-1989
  - Artist Cards, 1952-1989; 5.1; Archival Resource Key; 4.2 Linear feet Boxes 34-38
    Artist cards documenting artworks held by the gallery by artist. Information on cards include title, price, date, size, media, exhibition dates, loans, and occasionally the names of clients.
    - 1950s Artists, Avedisian through Drexler, 1952-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - 1950s Artists, Feeley through Freilicher, 1952-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - 1950s Artists, Georges, Goodnough, 1952-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - 1950s Artists, Goodnough, 1952-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - 1950s Artists, Hartigan, 1949-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - 1950s Artists, Hennessy through Richenburg, Rivers, 1952-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - 1950s Artists, Rivers, 1952-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Altoon, John, 1968-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Andre, Carl; Alpuy, Julio; Avery, Milton, 1965-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Bannard, Walter Darby, 1965-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Beal, Sondra; Boterf, Check, 1962-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Bowling, Frank; Bowman, Ken, 1965-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Boxer, Stanley, 1970-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Brody, Joel; Budd, David, 1964-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Brown, Deborah; Butler, James, 1984-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Bultman, Fritz, 1962-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Castoro, Rosemarie; Chiriani, Richard, 1966-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Ciarrocchi, Ray; Cohen, Larry, 1971-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Cornell, Joseph; Crawford, Thom Cooney, 1963-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Davis, Ron; De Kooning, Elaine, 1965-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Drexler, Sherman; Dzubas, Friedel; Evans, Garth, 1962-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Forakis, Peter; Forsman, Chuck, 1962-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Francis, Sherron; Frankenthaler, Helen, 1970-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Freilicher, Jane, 1963-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Getz, Ilse; Gordon, Harvey, 1962-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Goodnough, Robert, 1962-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 1-7)
    - Gourevitch, Jacqueline; Greenleaf, Ken, 1970-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Grillo, John; Gorchov, Ron; Gross, James, 1963-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Hartigan, Grace; Hatcher, Brower; Hennessy, Timothy; Hirsch, Gilah; Hood, Dorothy, 1960-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Hornak, Ian, 1970-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Houston Branch, 1975-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Hudson, Andrew, 1977-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Hughto, Darryl, 1971-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Jarden, Richards; Jones, Christopher, 1983-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Kozloff, Joyce, 1970-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 3-4)
    - Kalina, Richard; Kirschen-Cole, Stephanie; Lasker, Jonathan, 1979-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Le Comte, Mia, 1962-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Magisto, Chuck, 1979-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Mahdavi, Rafael, 1977-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Marshall, Dan, 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Milkowski, Antoni; Miller, Mariann Loveland; Miscellaneous Artists, 1961-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Moses, Forrest, 1975-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Park, Darragh, 1986-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Rand, Archie, 1979-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Richenburg, Robert, 1962-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Rivers, Larry, 1962-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Rivers, Larry, 1962-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Robbin, Tony; Rubenstein, Ephraim, 1985-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Shannon, Joe, 1980-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 3-4)
    - Stein, Ronnie; Tillim, Sidney, 1964-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Tum Suden, Richard, 1963-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 6-7)
    - Utterback, Robin, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Wilson, Jane, 1962-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 9-11)
    - Wisseman-Widrig, Nancy; Woodman, Betty; Youkilis, Edward, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Works Returned to Artist, 1964-1989; 5.2; Archival Resource Key; 1.9 Linear feet Boxes 38-40
    These cards document artworks that were returned to the artist and no longer in the gallery's possession. Information on cards may include title, date, size, media, date received and date returned.
    - Artworks to Return, Not in Computer, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Bannard, Walter Darby; Boxer, Stanley, 1975-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Bowling, Frank, 1976-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Bowman, Ken; Brown, Deborah, 1977-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Butler, Jim; Castoro, Rosemarie, 1971-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 1-3)
    - Chiriani, Richard; Ciarrocchi, Ray, 1976-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 4-5)
    - Evans, Garth; Forsman, Chuck; Goodnough, Robert, 1976-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Gregor, Harold; Hungarian Avant Garde, 1980-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Hunter, Paul; Jarden, Richards; Kirschen-Cole, Stephanie; Lorentzen, Ida, 1978-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Moynihan, Rodrigo; Mueller, Stephen, 1970-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Muller, Yvonne, 1976-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 11-12)
    - Nick, George; Noland, Kenneth; Nilsen, Ulf, 1977-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 13-14)
    - Norfolk, Geoffrey; Nozkowski, Tom; Ostlihn, Barbro; Patterson, Patricia, 1965-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Pereire, Emmanuel; Pollock, Jackson; Poulos, Basilios, 1965-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Purcell, Ann, 1977-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 17-18)
    - Rand, Archie, 1977-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Reginato, Peter, 1977-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Reich, Murray; Robbin, Tony, 1971-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Romberg, Osvaldo; Rose, Leatrice, 1975-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Rosenblatt, Adolph; Ross, Clifford; Rubenstein, Ephraim, 1976-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 5-6)
    - Saito, Kikuo; Scott, Sam; Scott, Tim; Schwedler, William; Shaw, Kendall; Stephan, Gary, 1964-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Terry, Robert; Thomson, Colin; Tillim, Sidney; Torres, Horacio; Twenty-fifth Anniversary, 1975-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Wissemann-Widrig, Nancy, 1977-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 9-10)
  - Sales, 1963-1989; 5.3; Archival Resource Key; 1.4 Linear feet Boxes 41-42
    These cards document artworks that were sold by the gallery. Information on the cards may include title, date, media, date purchased, customer/buyer name, price sold, and date shipped.
    - Alpuy, Bowling, Bowman, Boxer, 1975-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Bannard, Walter Darby, 1965-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 12-13)
    - Brown, Butler, Castoro, Chiriani, 1971-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Ciarrocchi, Ray, 1976-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Cohen, Crawford, De Kooning, Evans, 1976-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Forsman, Fox, Francis, 1979-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Golubov, 1976-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
    - Goodnough, Greenleaf, Gregor, 1976-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 3-5)
    - Gross, Holland, Hudson, Hughto, Hunter, 1971-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Jarden, Kalina, Kirschen-Cole, 1978-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 7-8)
    - Lasker, Lorentzen, Magisto, Mahdavi, 1977-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, Moses, Muller, 1977-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Nick, George, 1977-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Patterson, Park, Poulos, Purcell, Rand, 1977-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Reginato, Robbin, Romberg, Rose, 1975-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Rubenstein, Shannon, Schwedler, Torres, 1975-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Tum Suden, Welliver, 1963-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Utterback, Wisseman-Widrig, 1976-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - General Inventory, 1962-1989; 5.4; Archival Resource Key; 1.5 Linear feet Boxes 42-43
    Records and cards documenting clients, collectors, consignments, and loans. Materials may include information such as client or collector name, their artistic interests, exhibition information, as well as loan agreements and shipping receipts. Also included are general inventory logs.
    - Client Cards A through Z, 1977-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 1-5)
    - Collector Cards, circa 1977-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Consignment Cards, 1980-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 7-8)
    - Consignments Returned, 1970-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 9-15)
    - Consignments Returned, 1981-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 1-5)
    - Inventory Sheets, 1964-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 6-10)
    - Paintings on Loan Approval Consignment, 1966-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Paintings Returned from Loan Consignment, 1962-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 12-18)
- Houston Branch Records, 1969-1984; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 1.2 Linear feet Boxes 43-45
  Houston branch records include announcements, clippings, correspondence, financial information including consignments, income, invoices, and statements, photographs, publicity materials and a research file on Houston art museums.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Announcements and Invitations, 1973-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 19-21)
  - Artists Biographies and Information, circa 1969-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Clippings, 1973-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 23-24)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 25-26)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 1-4)
  - Financial - Miscellaneous - Consignments, Statements, Price Lists etc., 1972-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 5-6)
  - Financial - Invoices, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Financial - Statements, 1972-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Financial - Statements, 1972-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
  - Photographs - Gallery, 1973, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Plans & Drawings - Architectural, 1969-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Publicity, 1970-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Research - Houston Museums, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Exhibition Announcements, 1953-2016; Series 7; Archival Resource Key; 0.8 Linear feet Boxes 47-48
  Exhibition announcements promote the gallery's exhibitions for artists including Joe Brainard, Shirley Jaffe, Fairfield Porter, Rosemarie Castoro, Alfred Leslie, and many others.
  - Exhibition Announcements, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1953-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 2-3)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1970-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 4-5)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 2000-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 2-3)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 2010-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 4)